

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

#### Address

os. Kolorowe 4/12 31-938 Kraków

#### Contact

+48 696 051 742 teresa.j.gajewska@gmail.com

#### www

teresagajewska.pl

#### Github

github.com/tgajewska

#### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS



Bootstrap 4



JavaScript, jQuery



Webpack



Ajax



GIT



Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator



## **LANGUAGES**

English (CAE Cert.)



Russian



# TERESA GAJEWSKA

#### **PROFILE**

Over the last four years I have worked in the web development company, where I cooperated with developers and I became familiar with their job. Some time ago, I decided to change my career path. I began by learning the fundamentals of front-end technologies, such as HTML, CSS, SCSS, and JavaScript. Over the last few months I have been creating the front-end layer of a variety of web pages for my last employer.

I am actively in search of new career opportunities as a web developer.

# **PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS:**

- szwajcariakaszubska.com
- it.znin.pl
- westisthebest.treespot.pl
- "Czas na Świętokrzyskie" (unpublished yet)
- "Obserwator żubrów" (unpublished yet)

## **EXPERIENCE**

06.2018 - 12.2018

Amistad Sp. z o.o.

front-end developer

creating front-end layer of web pages (HTML, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery)

2014 - 2018

Amistad Sp. z o.o.

project manager

coordination of the work of the publishing and software development departments

2013 - 2014

#### Panczakiewicz Art Design

graphic designer, desktop publishing worker

2008 - 2013

#### First work experiences

project manager in Bezdroża Publishing House (2008-2010), payment processing at HSBC Service Delivery (2012-2013)

#### **EDUCATION**

2003 - 2008

Jagiellonian University, Kraków

Polish philology, master degree

#### **HOBBIES**





Bicycle touring Backpacking (Europe, Asia)